She did it 193 times.
Blue-Eyed Butcher is a drama, crime, thriller film directed by Stephen Kay.
A woman appeared to have a fairy-tale life, but six years into her marriage, the fairytale crumbles
when her husband is found buried in the backyard of their home with numerous stab wounds.
Susan Wright, played by Sara Paxton.
Jeff Wright, played by Justin Bruening.
Thomas Dean, played by W. Earl Brown.
Ron Wright, played by Michael Gross.
Susan's Mother, played by Lucinda Jenney.
Mrs. Wright, played by Annie Corley.
Blue Eyed Butcher is a 2012 American crime drama  thriller
television film directed by Stephen Kay.
It stars Sara Paxton, Justin Bruening and Lisa Edelstein.
The film is based on the 2003 stabbing death of Jeff Wright by the hands of his wife,
Susan Wright, but focuses on Kelly Siegler, the case's prosecutor.
The film made its debut on March 3, 2012, on Lifetime.
It later aired in France on the TF1 channel under the title 193 coups de folie.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship, suspicion of
murder, based on true story, multiple stabbings.
The tone is emotional and intense.